很快就天黑了
It'll be dark soon.
不远了
It's not much further.
我们有人可以帮她包扎
We have people who can patch her up.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
标记回去的路线
I'm marking our way back.
-你左边  -我来
- On your left!  - I've got it.
-丹尼尔  -克尔顿
- Daniel. - Colton.
很好
Good.
我们一直在找你们
We've been looking for you.
看来你们自己也找到了一些人
It looks like you found some people yourself.
我睡了多久了
How long have I been asleep?
差不多两天
Two days, more or less.
我们在哪
Where are we?
医生说你在好转
Doctor says you're healing up --
说情况本可能更糟糕
said it could have been much worse,
但你很幸运
but you had some luck.
你身上带着武器
And your pack with the weapons --
他们想把武器锁起来
they wanted to lock them up.
既然他们在帮我们  我就没反驳
Seeing as they were helping us, I didn't argue.
我们走之前  武器都要交给他们保管
It'll be with them until we're ready to leave.
我想那得还要一周
I figure that'll be another week,
也许时间更长
maybe a little more,
然后我们就能动身回亚历山大了
and then we can start back to Alexandria.
-这是什么地方  -这里的人们
- What is this place? - Well, the people here...
称这个地方为"神之国"
they, um, they call this place "The Kingdom."
他们在帮你
They were helping you...
所以我在帮他们
so I've been helping them.
你跟他们说了我的经历
Did you -- Did you tell them about what happened to me,
和我们的身份吗
about who we are?
怎么了  我们是谁  卡萝尔
Why? Who are we, Carol?
你怎么跟他们说的
What did you tell them?
他们看见了那男人对你做的事
They saw what that man did to you,
也看见了我对他做的事
and they saw what I did to him.
我们分开了
We got split up.
你惹上了麻烦  我找到了你
You found trouble. I found you.
他就知道这么多
That is all he knows.
他是谁
All who knows?
我要带你去见的人
The man I'm taking you to see --
管这里的人
the person who's in charge of this place.
这人有名字吗
This person have a name?
-摩根  -嗯
- Morgan? ?- Yeah.
他
He, um...
他叫"以西结国王"
...he's called "King Ezekiel."
什么
What?
是的
Yeah.
以西结国王
King Ezekiel.
而且
And, um...
他有自己的一套
he does his own thing.
明白吗
See?
那是什么意思
Uh, what does that mean?
好吧
Well...
我们到了
here we are.
对
Yeah.
我忘记说了
I, uh, I forgot to say that...
以西结有只老虎
Ezekiel has a tiger.
《行尸走肉》
希瓦  够了
Shiva, enough.
这位淑女经历了诸多磨难
The fair maiden has been through a myriad of trials.
他们是我们的客人
They are our guests.
冷静点  希
Chill it up, "S."
冷静点
Chill it up!
杰瑞  你是个忠诚的管家
Jerry, you are a faithful steward,
但你的话让我很困惑
but your words leave me pitch-kettled.
我理解你的担心  希瓦
I understand your concern, Shiva.
你没有见过卡萝尔
You haven't met Carol.
我也没有
Nor have I.
但既然她是摩根的朋友
But if she is a friend of Morgan,
我们该把她视为神之国的朋友
we shall consider her a friend of the realm
除非有相反证据
until proven otherwise.
她好转了
She's doing better,
多亏了你和你的人  所以
thanks to you and your people, so...
的确
Indeed.
看见你能起床走动  我很高兴  卡萝尔
It pleases me to see you up and about, Carol.
我是以西结国王
I am King Ezekiel.
欢迎来到神之国
Welcome to the Kingdom.
国王与你说话  你却一言不发
You have been addressed by the king, yet you remain silent.
是因为你心存疑虑吗
Do I detect skepticism?
也许你以为我疯了
Perhaps you think me mad.
也许你以为这个地方不过是镜花水月
Perhaps you see this place as nothing more than a mirage.
告诉我...
So...tell me...
你是怎么看待神之国的  卡萝尔
what do you think of The Kingdom, Carol?
又是怎么看待本王的
What do you think of the King?
我...觉得您棒极了
I...think you're amazing.
真是棒极了
It's amazing.
还有您的希巴...
And your Sheba --
它叫"希瓦"
It's, uh, "Shiva."
希瓦
Shiva.
棒极了
Amazing.
我差点惊得说不出话来
I would be speechless if I wasn't already speaking.
我不知道这到底是怎么回事
I don't know what the hell's going on
但我的喜大于惊
in the most wonderful way.
如同摩根所知
As Morgan is aware,
我鼓励那些在此修养的人
I encourage those who find respite here
随时享用我们这伟大的一切
to enjoy the fruits of our grandeur for as long as they like,
只要他们有所贡献
so long as they contribute.
取水于井  还井以水
Drink from the well, replenish the well...
当然  等你好了之后
once you've healed, of course.
当然
Of course.
当然  井养最重要
Of course. All about the well.
说得井辟
Well-said.
杰瑞...
Jerry...
我的待客之道呢
Ah, where are my manners?
请尽情吃吧
Please, partake.
我们有美味的苹果  油桃  石榴
We have magnificent apples, nectarines, pomegranates --
全都是在神之国里种的
all grown right here inside the Kingdom.
该吃水果了
It's fruit time.
我不能
I-I couldn't.
吃吧
Oh, come, now.
至少吃个石榴吧
At least take a pomegranate.
我总是觉得吃这个太麻烦了
You know, I always found them too much trouble.
苦皮包甜果
Sweet fruit surrounded by bitter --
是挺矛盾的
they're something of a contradiction,
但这也是天意
but heaven for the effort.
放些巧克力在我面前  我马上就能吃光
You park some chocolate in front of me and watch it go bye-bye,
但是石榴...我真不太喜欢  谢谢了
but pomegranates -- just not for me, thanks.
假如你有什么需要...
Well, if there's anything you want or need --
假如你喜欢音乐
if you enjoy music,
我们有一位吉他手  他的演奏催人泪下
we have a guitarist whose talent brings tears to the eye,
我们还有个小合唱团
and we have a small choir.
谢谢
Thank you.
我唯一需要的就是多休息
All I need is some more rest...
也许还需要一把梳子
and maybe a hairbrush.
没人告诉我要觐见王室
No one told me I'd be meeting royalty.
总而言之
Anyway...
陛下
uh, Your Majesty --
我是应该称您为"陛下"吧
I should call you "Your Majesty," right?
你可以这么称呼
You can.
谢谢您  陛下
Thank you, Your Majesty.
我深感荣幸
It's a pleasure.
我也很荣幸  卡萝尔
The pleasure is mine, Carol.
保重
Be well.
听着  我知道
Look, I know.
你是在逗我是吧
You're shitting me, right?
这...很难接受
Now, it's -- it's a lot.
他...
He is, um...
我不知道该怎么说...
I don't know. It -- It --
停下  别说了
Stop it. Stop this.
这地方跟个马戏团似的
This place is a damn circus --
这一切
all of it.
这些人...活在童话中
Th-These people -- this is make-believe.
就像在玩游戏
It's playtime.
而你就...
And you're just...
我做不来  我不能待在这里
I can't do this. I can't be here.
听着  卡萝尔  这些人找到了...
Look, Carol, these people found --
不  我待不下去  摩根
No, I can't, Morgan.
我也不会待下去
I won't.
我会等待时机
I'll wait.
等到你不在身边  没法阻止我了
And when you're not there to stop me,
等到没人能阻止我了  我就走
when nobody else is, I'll go.
你知道我不能让你走
You know I can't let you.
不  我会...
No. I'll --
你要怎样
You'll what?
像那个狼一样把我绑起来吗
Tie me up like that wolf?
是这样吗
Is that it?
这由不得你来决定
It isn't up to you.
之前在地下室里不是
It wasn't before in the basement,
在图书馆时不是  现在也不是
it wasn't at the library, and it isn't now.
我根本不在乎
I don't give a shit
你是否自认为找到了生命的奥秘
if you think you've found the secret to life.
-我... -不  我没有这么认为
- I -- ?- No, I don't. I don't.
我没有  我也没找到  我知道我引发了什么
I don't, and I haven't. And I know what I've started.
但我不会让你死在外面的
But I won't let you die out there.
那是我不会做的事
That's what I won't do.
你做什么并不重要
It doesn't matter what you do.
我们去哪儿
Where we going?
-打猎  -猎捕什么
- Hunting. - Hunting what?
曾经被关在农场的东西
What was once captive to the farm
现在在城里自由奔驰
now runs free in the city.
这边
?Here!
快  快跑
Come on! Come on!
快  快点  跟上
-快跑  -快点
- Come on!  - Come on!
转弯  转弯  快走
Turn! Turn! Whoo, whoo! ?Come on!
走  快走
Go now! Go now!
-走  快走  -快点
- Go now! Go now! - Come on!
快走  快走  快点
Go now! Go now! Go! ?Come on! Go!
好样的  理查德
Well-done, Richard.
那是我们需要的
It's just what we needed.
为什么要用行尸
Why the Walker?
我们在赶它们进去  你为什么还需要诱饵
We're herding them in. Why do you need bait?
因为我希望它们的肚子里装满腐肉
Because I want their bellies full of rot.
这就是原因
That's why.
你在深山老林里开机枪  不会招来任何东西
You shoot a machine gun in the woods, and nothing.
但如果在城里咳一声  就...
You cough in the city, and...
黛安  去把货车开来
Diane, retrieve the truck.
我们马上离开
We'll take our leave.
本
Ben...
该你上了
you're up.
用砍刀
Use the machete.
就像你和他练习时那样
Just as you and he have practiced.
好的
Yeah.
像我们练习时那样
Like we practiced.
不要觉得不安  本杰明
Do not be troubled, Benjamin.
下次就好了
Next time.
不要让家里的人知道这事
No one back home needs to know about this.
你是说这些猪吃腐尸的事吗
You mean the pigs -- that they're eating the dead?
任何事都别提
Any of it.
愿我们有一天能解除你们所有人的诅咒
May we one day cease you all from this curse!
在那之前  要知道我们生活在你们的土地上
Till then, know that we live on in your place...
充实  忠诚  自由
full, festive, faithful, and free.
只能算半自由
Only halfway free.
他们去哪儿
Where are they going?
别的地方
Somewhere else.
你使用棍杖的技能
Your skill with the staff...
你是怎么掌握这种技能的
how did you come to acquire that skill?
一个做奶酪的朋友教我的
It was a cheesemaker, a friend.
我相信如今你的同伴一定非常以你为傲吧
I imagine your comrade would be very proud of you this day.
一击就救了本的命
For saving Ben in a single blow.
有这么一种说法
There's a saying --
悲观主义者向下看  磕到了脑袋
the pessimist looks down and hits his head.
乐观主义者向上看
The optimist looks up...
失去了立足点
and loses his footing.
现实主义者向前看
The realist looks forward
根据前方的情况调整自己的路线
and adjusts his path accordingly.
我觉得小本杰明的路线  就需要调整
I believe young Benjamin's path is in need of adjustment.
你能训练他吗
Would you train him,
就像你的朋友训练你那样
as your friend trained you?
我不...
I don't...
我不知道我是否是适合...
I don't know that I'm the --
本杰明在刀枪上没有造诣
Benjamin has shown aptitude with neither blades nor munitions.
也许他失败的原因在于武器
Perhaps his failings lie in the weapons...
也许在于师父
perhaps it's the teacher...
也许两者都有
and perhaps it's both.
听着  知道吗
Hey, look, you know...
我开枪才救下了卡萝尔
the man I shot to save Carol,
棍杖救不了她
the stick couldn't have saved her.
棍杖救过你吗
Has it saved you?
是的
Yeah.
小本杰明要成为我这里的重要一员
Young Benjamin will become an important member of my court.
我要那孩子...
I need the boy to...
我要他活下去
I need him to live.
拜托了
Please.
好吧
Okay.
神之国再次为你的到来而高兴
The Kingdom is favored by your presence once more!
(取水于井  还井以水)
刚才太快了是吧
That was too fast, right?
不不  我能跟上
No, no, I can keep up.
不不
No, no.
太快了
It's too fast.
-打头  -打头
- Over the head? - Over the head.
对  再来
There. And again.
向后抡  上举
Swing it back and up.
口味层层叠加
I mean, it was flavor on top of flavor.
简直太梦幻了
It was like a goddamn dream.
早餐吃酥皮水果馅饼  真是...
I mean, breakfast cobbler? That's...
我们以前可是靠吃负鼠充饥
We were eating possum out there.
我更喜欢午餐吃酥皮水果馅饼
Now, I like the lunch cobbler.
午餐还有酥皮水果馅饼
There's lunch cobbler?
我们每顿都有酥皮水果馅饼
We have cobbler at every meal.
我有点...
I'm just so...
我不能...天啊  老天
I just...I can't. Oh, God! Oh, geez.
你有纸巾吗
Do you have any tissues?
有  稍等
Yeah, one second.
那是什么书
Hey, what's the book?
是...哲学书
It's, uh...It's philosophy.
咱们真的得
You know, we should really get back to...
-继续练习了  -借我看看行吗
- what we were doing. - You mind if I borrow it?
这里所有的书我都读过了  两遍
I've just read every book in this place...twice...
包括空调维修说明书
Including an air-conditioning repair textbook.
知道吗  供热通风与空气调节系统
Just so you know, the number-one problem
最大的问题其实不是致冷剂泄漏
with an H.V.A.C. system isn't refrigerant leaks.
对
Yeah.
不给你剧透了
Won't spoil that one for you.
可以吗
Please?
给
Here.
先生们
Gentlemen...
跟我们来  你们俩都来
come with us, both of you.
我们有很重要的事要处理
We have matters of import to attend to.
把你枪带上  摩根
Bring your gun, Morgan.
猪是在离神之国很远的地方被屠宰的
The swine are slaughtered far from The Kingdom...
以免他们的叫声招致麻烦
lest their screams carry in the wind and invite questions.
我们在这里做的事对我的人保密
What we are doing here is a secret I keep from my people.
有些人把秘密当作是统治的特权
Some see secrets as a privilege of ruling.
它们是障碍  不是奖赏
They are burdens, not part of the reward.
它们是代价
They are the cost.
我还担心我们来早了
Here, I was worried we were early.
我对我们的协议非常认真
Our arrangement is something I consider with the utmost seriousness.
每一次都会准时履行义务
We will fulfill our obligations on time, every time.
你确实如此  你以后也会
Yes, indeedy, you do, and you will.
一二三四五六七八  一共八只  很好
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. I count 8 -- that's good.
它们比上次更肥大  这也很好
They look bigger than last time. That's good, too.
它们吃得很好
They were well-fed.
我亲自确认的
I made sure of it.
多谢你们款待
We appreciate your hospitality.
幸运的是  我们开了两辆卡车来
Lucky for us, we brought two trucks.
不如你们来帮忙装货如何
How about you, uh, help us load 'em up?
他们是另一伙人
They're part of another group.
-他们自称...  -我知道他们是谁
- They call themselves  - I know who they are.
混蛋  笑一个不好吗
Hey, asshole, how about a smile?
这不算什么
This -- This is nothing.
我们是便宜你们了
We've been letting you off easy.
你确定你没搞反吗  小子
You sure you don't have that backwards, kid?
是的
Yeah.
我确定
I'm sure.
停手
Cease this.
把武器放下
Lower your weapons.
理查德
Richard...
放开他
let him go.
这不是我们的作风
This is not what we do.
自由罚拳吗
Free shot?
我喜欢这个
Oh, I love this shit.
加文  让你的人住手
Gavin, tell your man to stop.
-加文  -他说住手
?- Gavin! - Hey! Hey! The man said stop!
他对我们很好
And he's been good to us.
我们已经浪费他足够多时间了
We've taken up more than enough of his time.
理查德  我们会讨论这事  起来吧
Richard, we will discuss this. Come on.
下周同样的时间  以西结  可以吗
Same time next week, Ezekiel, all right?
是生产周  那就生产起来
It's produce week, so...produce.
你有单子  一点不能少
You got the list -- not one bit less.
否则  你懂的
Otherwise...you know...
第一个拿他开刀
he's gonna have to go first.
你以前遇到过他们吗
You've encountered them before?
他们一伙人吗
Their group?
遇到过
Yeah.
你为了救卡萝尔杀的那个人
The man you killed to save Carol --
也是他们中的一员
he was one of them, as well?
是  没错
He was, yeah.
这就是你要我来的原因吗
Is that why you wanted me here --
因为如果有必要我可以再做一次吗
because I could do it again if I had to?
不  摩根
No, Morgan.
事实恰好相反
Quite the opposite, in fact.
等等
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
你要去哪
Where you going, hmm?
今晚是电影之夜
It's movie night tonight.
我想占个好座位
I want to get a good seat.
好  但你先得把东西吃干净
Right, but you were gonna clean your plate, though, first.
快点  说好的  达奇
Come on. That was the deal, Dutch.
吃掉
Yeah. ?
很好  很聪明
Wow. Good one, smart guy.
好吧  十点前上床
All right, well, just be in bed by 10:00 --
一分钟不许迟
not a minute later.
但我可以看书
But I can read?
对  你可以看书
Yes, you can read.
好了
All right.
他是个好孩子
He's a good kid.
没错
Yeah. Yeah, he is.
我对如何抚养他一知半解
I only kind of know what I'm doing raising him.
以西结帮了很大的忙
Ezekiel's been a big help.
你和国王
You seem close...
关系好像很好
you and the King.
是啊  他曾经和我爸爸关系很好
Yeah, he was, uh, pretty tight with my dad.
我父亲曾经是一名优秀的战士
My father was a good fighter.
神之国最好的战士之一
One of the best in The Kingdom.
发生了什么
How'd it happen?
大概一年前
It was about a year ago.
以西结派他的小队去扫清一幢大楼
Ezekiel sent his detachment out to clear out a building.
行尸太多  增援不够
There was too many wasted and not enough backup.
有八个人死在了里面
Eight men didn't make it out.
其中就有我父亲
My father was one of 'em.
但是以西结...他现在谨慎多了
But E-Ezekiel -- he's a lot more careful now.
他告诉我...
He told me that it, uh, well...
他告诉我他暗中和那个团队达成协议
He, uh, told me he was keeping his deal with that group quiet
因为他觉得人们会想要反抗
'cause he thinks the people would want to fight.
他说就算我们反抗  也不会赢
He says that even if we did, we wouldn't win --
至少不可能不死人
at least, not without losing people...
也许会损失很多人
maybe a lot of 'em.
你觉得他是对的
And you think he's right...
我们不该反抗
that we shouldn't fight?
我不知道  我是说...
I don't know. I mean...
我知道的太少  不知道应该怎么样
I don't know if I know enough to know.
也许你知道
Maybe you do.
那本书里有一段题词
There was an inscription in the book.
是手写的  是说不杀戮的
It was handwritten -- about not killing.
-是你写的吗  -不是
- Is it yours? - It's not, no.
因为我还注意到
'Cause I also noticed
你晚餐只吃蔬菜
you only put vegetables on your plate during dinner.
我是说  你还教我合气道
And, I mean, you're teaching me aikido,
如果合气道的意义是不杀戮
and if aikido means not to kill,
-那也就是说你...  -跟我怎么想的无关
- then that means that you're... - It's not about what I think.
人们能...
People can --
他们能努力让你走上正道
They can try and set you in the right direction,
但他们没法教你该走那条路
but they can't show you the way.
你得自己去寻找...
You know, you got to find that for yourself, and...
我曾以为我找到了
I thought I had it.
真的
I did.
但我  我还在摸索
But I'm -- I'm just fumbling through.
有时我们会改变主意
Sometimes, we change our minds.
你今晚想看电影吗
Well, hey, do you want to catch movie night?
不行
I can't.
我...
I, uh...
我得找卡萝尔谈谈
I got to talk to Carol.
不过谢谢你
But thank you.
随你所愿  淑女
By all means, fair maiden.
摘一个吧
Have one.
这个院子
This enclosure was built
原本是为了娱乐和学习所建造的
for the purpose of common recreation and study.
我改造成了一个花园  甚为辉煌
I had it repurposed into a garden worthy of our splendor.
我敢说这是我在整个神之国中最喜欢的地方
I dare say it's my favorite place in the entire Kingdom.
在你决定突然离开我们之前
It pleases me that you've seen it with your own eyes
能亲眼看看这里  我真的很高兴
before...choosing to leave us so suddenly.
天  我...
Geez, yeah, I...
我真的很抱歉
I'm real sorry about this.
只是...
Um, it's just...
我在这里有什么用
What good am I here?
杰瑞  能让我们单独聊聊吗
Jerry... would you excuse us?
如果您需要我  就叫一声
If you need me, holler.
我随叫随到
I keep in hollering range.
和平
Deuces!
如果我现在没有碰巧遇见你...
If I hadn't happened upon you right now...
那句话怎么说的来着
What's that saying?
不要骗一个骗子
Never bullshit a bullshitter.
没说错吧
Have I got that right?
你装出温柔无辜的样子...
The sweet-and-innocent act you've been doing --
很聪明
it's quite clever.
我信了
Worked on me.
你混进来  赢得别人的信任
Blend in, get people to trust you,
得到你想要的东西
acquire what you need from them,
然后你就消失了  就像从没来过
and then you're gone, as if you were never there.
你带到这里的那些枪
The guns you brought here in your pack
是救世军的
they belong to Saviors.
你对救世军知道多少
What do you know about the Saviors?
很不幸  比我在乎的还多
More than I care to, unfortunately.
他们差点杀了你
They nearly extinguished you.
但你不单奋起反抗了  卡萝尔  你赢了
But you did more than put up a fight, Carol -- you won.
来到这里就算赢了吗
By ending up here?
你觉得这很搞笑吗
That's funny to you?
你就是个笑话  这个地方也是
You're a joke. This place is.
对待笑话就得一笑而过
That's what you do with jokes -- you laugh.
在外面  外面的世界才是真的
Out there -- Out there, it's real.
我到过一些地方  让我以为我可以无需...
I've been to places where I thought I wouldn't have to --
可以安心过生活
where I could just be.
你是在用童话骗这些人
You're selling these people a fairy tale.
或许他们就需要童话
Maybe they need the fairy tale.
或许就是需要否认现实
Maybe the contradiction is the point.
统治他人
And ruling over people
让人对你溜须拍马只是额外的好处吗
and having your ass kissed by everyone's just a perk?
我能坐这吗
May I?
人们需要可以追随的人
People want someone to follow.
这是人的天性
It's human nature.
他们想要能让自己觉得安全的人
They want someone to make 'em feel safe.
有安全感的人也就没那么危险
And people who feel safe are less dangerous...
更有生产力
more productive.
他们看到了个养老虎的人
They see a dude with a tiger, shoot --
就开始疯传他在野外找到老虎
they start tellin' stories about finding it in the wild,
一番搏斗后驯服成他的宠物
wrestling it into submission, turning it into his pet.
他们把这人变成了一个传奇
They make the guy larger than life,
一个英雄
a hero.
我怎么能击碎他们的幻想
And who am I to burst their bubble?
接下来  他们就视我为王室
Next thing you know, they treat me like royalty.
他们想要  也需要一个人去追随
They wanted --They needed someone to follow,
所以我就配合演出
s-so I-I acted the part.
装模作样直到真成了那么回事
I faked it till I made it.
我以前是个动物园管理员
I was a zookeeper.
希瓦  她掉进了她展区的防护河里
Shiva -- she fell into one of the concrete moats in her exhibit.
里面没水  兽医在来的路上
It was empty, the vets were on their way,
但她的腿被撕开了
but her leg was ripped open.
她会失血过多而死
She was gonna bleed out.
当时她发出的叫声
The sound she made...
她痛得不行
She was in so much pain.
我知道有风险
I knew the risk.
但我得试试
I had to try.
我把我衣服绑在她腿上
And I got my shirt up around her leg...
救了她一命
saved her life.
那之后  她见到我
After that, she never showed
连牙都不会呲
so much as a tooth in my direction.
养老虎确实不现实  这我知道
Keeping a tiger isn't practical -- I know.
她有十人份的食量
She eats as much as 10 people.
她能把我手中的铁链拽掉
She could yank the chain out of my hand --
老天  她甚至能把我胳膊拽下来
hell, she could yank my arm right off.
但她没有这么做
But she hasn't.
以后也不会这么做
She won't.
我跟其他人一样  都失去了很多
I lost a lot, just like everybody else.
当一切开始分崩离析时
When it all started to end,
我回到了动物园
I found myself back at the zoo.
希瓦是仅剩的几只动物之一
Shiva was one of the last animals left.
她被困住了
She was trapped...
饥肠辘辘  孤立无援
hungry, alone.
跟我一样
Like me.
她是这个世界上我仅存的挚爱
She was the last thing left in this world that I loved.
她保护了我
She protected me.
是她带我来的这  让我成为传奇
She got me here, made me larger than life.
然后我建了这个地方
And I made this place.
我以前在社区剧院表演过
I used to act in community theater --
演过几个国王
played a few kings in my day...
亚瑟王  麦克白
...Arthur, Macbeth...
还有马丁·路德
Martin Luther.
但我真名就叫以西结
My name really is Ezekiel, though.
千真万确
That's 100% real.
我把话摊开说了
Cards on the table.
没藏着掖着
Nothing up my sleeve.
不过我还是希望你不要透露给他人
I'd appreciate you keep this between us, though,
为了他们
for them.
也有点算是为了我
And, yeah, a little bit for me.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你想做什么随便
You do what you want.
我只想离开这
I just want to go.
去哪儿
Go where?
卡萝尔
Carol.
离开这
Away.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
为你所经历过的所有苦难
For whatever bad you've been through.
现在外面的苦难很多
There's so much of it out there now, you know?
太多了
Too much.
外面好像只剩下坏事了
Out there, it feels like it's all bad,
特别是当你孤身一人的时候
especially when you're alone.
但是  实际上
The thing is, though...
并不全是坏事
...it's not all bad.
不可能是  不是的
It can't be. It isn't.
生命并非如此
Life isn't.
有生命的地方  就有希望
Where there's life, there's hope,
有英雄气概  慈悲和爱
heroism, grace, and love.
有生命的地方  就有生活
Where there's life, there's life.
我希望这不是你想逃离的东西
I hope that's not what you're walking away from.
如果我是呢
So what if I am?
也许你不用这样
Maybe you don't have to.
我在这里创造了自己的世界
I made my own world here.
找到了应对困境的办法
I found a way to deal with the bad
那就是对美好的事物过分投入一点
by going a little overboard with all the good.
我只是
I just...
拥抱矛盾
embraced the contradiction.
也许你也可以  按你自己的方式
Maybe you could, too, in your own way.
比如你可以走  但同时不走
Like, maybe you could go and... not go.
没错  我听起来像个疯子
Yeah, I-I sound like a crazy person.
我懂
I get it.
或许我就是个疯子
You know, maybe I am.
但我想我能帮你
But I think I can help...
如果你允许的话
if you let me.
你为什么要在乎我
Why do you care?
因为这让我感觉很好
'Cause it makes me feel good.
我会把你的东西都装好
I'll get your stuff together,
找个我信任的人和你在门口碰头
find somebody I trust to meet you at the gate,
所以你可以走  也同时不走
so you can go and-- and not go.
我们看看  我是不是对的
We'll see if I'm on to something
还是说我又在胡说八道
or if it's just more bullshit.
你说呢
What do you say?
你确定这是你想要的吗
You're sure this is what you want, right?
我确定
I am.
听你的
It's up to you.
一直都应该由你自己决定
It should have always been up to you.
停
Whoa.
停下
行吗
Okay?
好了
Got it.
待在这
Stay there.
我们到了真好
It's good we're here.
怎么了
?How's that?
再多十分钟  我可能就要开始后悔
10 more minutes, and I might start to regret
我之前老想射你捅你了
all the times I tried to shoot and stab you.
我想你是我敲倒的人里我最喜欢的一个了
I think you're my favorite person I ever knocked out.
肯定能排到前二或前三
Definitely top two or three.
照顾好自己
Take care of yourself.
-我会的  -保证吗
- I will. - Do you promise?
时刻警惕  时刻准备好  记得吗
Always watching, always ready, remember?
我记得
I do.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
停下
Whoa.
你真的应该尝一下
You really got to try one of these.